damart.co.uk 2014-07-02

# None

| 

**Privacy Policy**

******Data Protection**  
The personal information we collect about you including your shopping habits is used by us to verify your identity, undertake credit assessments to inform our lending decisions, manage your account and to make collections. We may share information about you and the conduct of your account with credit reference agencies, with other lenders and with fraud prevention agencies. Under the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access the personal data we hold about you. Should you wish to do so, please write to The Data Protection Officer at Damart, Bowling Green Mills, Lime Street, Bingley, West Yorkshire BD97 1AD enclosing your payment of £10.00 for our administration. Please contact The Data Protection Officer if you have any reason to believe that data we hold about you is incorrect. _Top^_

******Use of your Email Address**  
When registering your email address, placing a catalogue request or when placing an order on our website, you must choose whether or not you wish to receive our e-newsletters. If you agree, you will be sent information about our products and special offers by email. If you no longer wish to receive these messages, you can cancel your subscription at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of each email or by contacting us via the form on the website. You may also be offered the chance to sign up to 3rd party email marketing should you wish. If you no longer wish to receive these proposals, simply contact us via this website or write to E-commerce Manager, Damart, Bowling Green Mills, Lime Street,. Bingley, West Yorkshire, BD97 1AD, with your name, address and customer account number if you have one. _Top^_

******Cookies (Updated)**  

**What are cookies?**  
A cookie is a simple text file stored on your computer that allows a website to recognise you when you return and to improve your experience as you move around the website and make a purchase. Cookies help us to display specially tailored information from our website so you have a more relevant online shopping experience with us, and they also save you from having to fill in all the information you provided at a previous visit, each time you come back to the site. They also help us analyse the usability of the website in order that we can ensure we're giving you the best possible experience and constantly improving things for you. We may also use 3rd party cookies to track the effectiveness of our online advertising and our email marketing campaigns.

**What cookies are used on this website?**  
When someone visits our website we collect standard internet log information. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the website, and how our customers are using the website. We collect this information so that we can constantly offer you the best service and it is collected in a way which does not personally identify you. 

If we do want to collect personally identifiable information at any point on the website we will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it. 

The table below provides an overview of all the cookies used on our website, the purpose of the cookie, when it expires and how you can find out further information about each cookie:

| Cookie | Purpose | 

Potential Intrusiveness

| 

**Expiry**  
  
---|---|---|---  
Damart cookie  | Remembers the content of your basket as you shop. This cookie is essential to the operation of the website. | 

**Low**

| 

At the end of your browser session  
  
Google Analytics

| Allows us to record how many visitors we have to the website and what pages are visited so that we can constantly improve our website for you | 

**Low**

| 

_[Visit the Privacy Policy of Google](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)_ to find out further information about these cookies.  
  
Doubleclick remarketing cookie | Allows us to deliver relevant marketing messages on 3rd party websites and the Google content network following a visit to our website | 

**Low**

| 

30 days  
  
Email Cookie | Allows us to track the effectiveness of our email marketing and ensure we're delivering the best offers to your inbox | 

**Low**

| 

Does not expire  
  
Sub2 Cookie | Sub2 use cookies to enhance the user experience with this site by delivering both personalised content and offers whilst ensuring you see the products most relevant to you. Any information collected is not shared with any other third parties. To learn more about these cookies, please [click here](http://webservices.sub2tech.com/optout/optout.asp) | 

**Low**

| 

At the end of your browser session  
  
**How do I manage cookies?**  
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, however you can turn them off in your browser preferences should you wish. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies by changing the add-on's settings.

For more information about cookies and instructions on how to adjust your browsers settings to accept, delete or reject cookies, see the IAB website [www.youronlinechoices.co.uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.co.uk/). The relevant page for adjusting your browser settings is at [www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/five-top-tips](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/five-top-tips).

**Please remember that, if you disable cookies, this will affect our ability to deliver a service through our website that is more tailored to you and you will be unable to place an order on our website.**

If you do leave cookies enabled, be sure to sign off when you finish if using a shared computer, so that the next user cannot access your information. _Top^_
